Guide to the Stanford University, Asian American Students Association, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Asian American Students Association, records
2013
SC1156
Stanford University. Asian American Students' Association.
646 megabyte(s)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Asian American students--California.; Asian Americans--California--Stanford; Asian Americans--California.; Asian Americans--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Listen to the Silence 2013; Click, Connect & Engage: From Social Media to Social Justice
  "Listen to the Silence" is Stanford's annual Asian American issues conference organized by the Asian American Students' Association (AASA). "Listen to the Silence" began at Stanford in 1995 out of the need to increase the visibility of Asian American issues and to educate those in the community and beyond about the conditions of the Asian American community. The conference goals have since expanded to include the empowerment of Asian American students to take direct action to improve their communities and work towards social justice. Through the various workshops hosted by students, nonprofits, and community leaders, the Listen to the Silence conference provides a platform for discussion about the intersections of history, identity, and social change to provide an avenue for taking action and creating cross-cultural and cross-campus coalitions. Ultimately, the Listen to the Silence conference aims to provide tangible tools and resources to inspire, educate, and empower participants to work towards creating a more equitable and fair society as part of the broader movement for social justice.
  - Co-Chairs, 2013; 54 computer file(s)
  - Concert, 2013; 7 computer file(s)
  - General Documents, 14 computer file(s)
  - Logistics, 2013; 25 computer file(s)
  - Meeting Notes (All Staff), 2013; 5 computer file(s)
  - Meeting Notes (Chairs), 2013; 10 computer file(s)
  - Pictures, 33 computer file(s)
  - Publicity, 2013; 49 computer file(s)
  - Workshops, 2013; 35 computer file(s)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - T-shirt (Box 1)